<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Scrambled]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Scrambled</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:17:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:17:16 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[The First Dragons]]></title><description><![CDATA[These <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> were the first to be born from <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> at the beginning of the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a>. The first to be born of these dragons was <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragunthar, the First Dragon" data-href="Dragunthar, the First Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/dragunthar,-the-first-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragunthar</a>, and the only defining property of these dragons was that they were capable of conscious thought. Aside from that, they did not resemble dragons in any way, at least not until dragons began to manipulate the Chaos and hold power over <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, which they then used to make more desirable forms for themselves that all other dragons descended from. This is why wyrms, drakes, wyverns, and so on all look somewhat different, as they are all differing descendants of The First Dragons.<br>
“There were 7 Dragons at the beginning of all, and it is said that all life sprung forth from their actions. Were it not for their shows of power, we would have never seen the powerful and fearsome Desecrator Aternos gift our world with unity. Without those improbable statistical wonders, we could not even possess a soul with which to cherish alongside others”
— <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Salgus, the Carrier" data-href="Salgus, the Carrier" href="remote-blog/characters/salgus,-the-carrier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Salgus</a>, upon meeting <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Havus, The First Prodigy" data-href="Havus, The First Prodigy" href="remote-blog/characters/havus,-the-first-prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Havus</a> for the first time.
]]></description><link>remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/The First Dragons.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yeva, the Stable Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yeva was one of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a> and became particularly concerned with the loss of what she deemed her friends after <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon" data-href="Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/kupaulus,-the-hidden-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kupaulus</a> was ‘killed’ by <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon" data-href="Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/zosciva,-the-flaming-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zosciva</a>, resulting in her creation of the <a data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a>.<br>Her construct of the Soul allowed The First Dragons hasty recovery from their deaths as opposed to taking a lengthy time to reforge their bodies after losing control of the <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> binding them from fatigue or force. For all other creatures that did not originally forge their body from Chaos and thus do not actively keep themselves bound, such as the future <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a>, death is more permanent and typically contains one’s energy into their Soul to allow a chance at having a new body be created by either themselves or another. This means Chaos dragons are typically immortal too, though they cannot recycle the same body in most instances, and if no one else helps them and they possess too little Chaos to create a new body, then they are still capable of being killed fully. All future creatures (including <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> born after the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>) simply cannot create themselves a new body at all when in a soul form and thus are mortal in comparison.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/yeva,-the-stable-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Yeva, the Stable Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nexhal]]></title><description><![CDATA[“Devourers of Chaos”Nexhal are serpent-like translucent space dwellers. They are born through the death of a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon</a> that then does not get reborn (as Dragons are not under the jurisdiction of <a data-href="Surturins" href="remote-blog/locations/surturins.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Surturins</a>, and have also existed long before its creation) and so the mind decays and the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Concepts/Soul" data-href="Concepts/Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a> erodes its seamless hold on the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magics/Magic" data-href="Magics/Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> of the deceased Dragon, thus creating the ethereal form of a Nexhal.<br>Nexhals have long worm-like bodies that can be seen through and have legs that are formed of two parts and make right angles at their joint (much like how a mantis holds its arms up) that run along the bottom of the creature like a centipede. These legs allow them to walk along <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> and or the strands of Magic. This means that, though they typically inhabit the zero-gravity realm of space, they still have full movement and within even expending Magic.<br>Nexhal exclusively eat Chaos in order to sustain themselves, and they prefer to travel in packs if possible. They will also attack any and all creatures that aren’t Dragons in the attempt to convert their forms into raw Chaos. The only way to kill a Nexhal is by disrupting the soul that contains its entire existence. Nexhal are the grotesque and unintended consequence of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Yeva, the Stable Dragon" data-href="Yeva, the Stable Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/yeva,-the-stable-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yeva’s</a> wish to allow her peers to have hastier recoveries from death.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/nexhal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Nexhal.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chaos Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[The most untainted magic, but also the most unpredictable. It is capable of anything, as it is forged from and utilizes <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a>. The more Chaos energy you utilize, the more you can accomplish, but without proper control things could go very wrong. With enough Chaos energy that embodies you, or if you were just born with proper control like in the cases of entities like <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a>, then you can begin to control the Chaos Magic more properly, but that weakens it greatly in turn.<br>Chaos Magic is generally inaccessible to any and all creatures born after the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>, save the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy" data-href="Prodigy" href="remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigies</a>. This is because Chaos energy is only used to form a newly born creature, but then it is unified after that point. Chaos is only used in the initial exchanges, it is no longer a final product to anything other than <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> and the Prodigies.Think of Chaos as a flowing river; you can see where it is flowing from and mentally rewind it to see how things came to be, but you cannot reverse the flow of this river. You can easily look to the farther end of the river, maybe swim downstream and make a ruckus, but you cannot swim upstream for the current is too strong. In this way, Chaos Magic cannot affect the past, it can only view the past. However, you could easily affect the future. Time and Chaos, just like space and time, are interwoven and this rule cannot be violated.]]></description><link>remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Magics/Chaos Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)]]></title><description><![CDATA[(79 DB - 111 DB)
Scramloria was created by <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a> alongside the <a data-href="Order of the Eclipse" href="remote-blog/factions/order-of-the-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Order of the Eclipse</a> with the goal to give people an escape from magic during the height of the <a data-href="Era of Prosperity" href="remote-blog/ages/era-of-prosperity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Era of Prosperity</a>. Of course, it was Xavier's secret goal to use it as a place to keep the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy Child</a> away from the rest of the world, and particularly his fellow <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Bearer of the Egg" data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearers of the Egg</a>.Scramloria was ruled based upon the strength of its people. They had a warrior culture that believed only the strongest would have the privilege of commanding others.<br><img alt="Map of Scramloria.png" src="remote-blog/locations/map-of-scramloria.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Scramloria (The Sunless Realm).md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Novum Optimus]]></title><description><![CDATA[Latin for "new/fresh" and "the best/aristocratic". This is a sprawling empire of magical ingenius led by all members of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Bearer of the Egg" data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearers of the Egg</a> save <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Novum Optimus.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Navu]]></title><description><![CDATA[Means "Dimension" in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>. This is the name given to the floating world that all life typically takes rest upon. Some exceptions to this are <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a>, .<br>As Navu forms, the farther out you go tends to have more uneven distributions of Chaos coming from the <a data-href="Anomaly" href="remote-blog/artifacts/anomaly.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Anomaly</a> and thus biomes like deserts or tundras form from lesser amounts of energy whereas things like forests can form with excess. Dead creatures with a lot of energy or things with a lot of energy in general can form into mountains or glaciers. These glaciers will overtime carve out landscapes like lakes and rivers. Water can generally form too but only as a result of storms that can stir up from heavier fluctuations deriving from the anomaly. Energy that radiates downwards has more pressure on it from what else has been formed and thus typically forms itself more into a rocky form, though it can become minerals or sometimes caves with similar things to the surface layer under proper conditions.<br>Energy that escapes upwards floats freely and glides across all that has already been created. This allows it to coalesce up higher, either forming clouds, getting trapped in a magical barrier equivalent to an atmosphere, or (in majority) ascends super high and clumps into the equivalent of a sun. This sun object has <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> flowing into it from different angles, propelling it around so that it revolves around the top side of Navu, meaning Navu never can become pitch dark and only increasingly close to such as the sun is always somewhere off in the distance, it never drops below a horizon or anything. This sun object isn’t quite like our own, and it works in a way where a majority of the light it produces gets cast beneath it in a cone, where as rays originating from higher up it would be progressively dimmer. This is because less chaos energy reaches the higher parts of the object as opposed to the bottom parts. However, the chaos that goes into it and moves it around can also cause it to rotate as an object slightly and can make the brightest parts of the sun aim in different directions than it usually would for some time before it settles to normal.A giant continent in the very center of Navu that holds the Anomaly and houses many powerful creatures due to the aforementioned artifact.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/navu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Navu.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magus Optimus]]></title><description><![CDATA[An ancient society that thrived upon their usage of <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a>. The <a data-href="Proto-Humans" href="remote-blog/races/proto-humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Proto-Humans</a> that inhabited this sprawling city focused on utilizing Magic to accomplish all their basic needs with as little effort as possible. This included making machines that use Magic in order to create the desired outcomes. However, it was shunned to rely on too much machinery, as Magic was viewed as the superior art form, and thus over reliance was punishable. A group of scholars dared to claim that machinery was an art that would take Magic to even greater heights, but they were all banished to far away lands that were then formed into <a data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthas</a>.<br>Magus Optimus, however, ran a long course of history, only ending when they began to gain interest in <a data-href="Draconic Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/draconic-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draconic Magic</a>. This caused <a data-href="Dragonia" href="remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragonia</a> to see Magus Optimus as a threat, as they believed that Magus Optimus would stop at no lengths to acquire and harvest <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> for their own gain. Given Dragonia's relationship with Dragons, they immediately waged war upon Magus Optimus, who despite their great power was not yet ready to fight against Dragons. Dragonia sent many Dragons over, but <a data-href="Siethun" href="remote-blog/characters/siethun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Siethun</a> was the Dragon that caused the most destruction, and was praised back in Dragonia for this.<br>The remnants of Magus Optimus became a variety of different smaller nations throughout time, but after the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a>, Magus Optimus was reinstated under the name <a data-href="Novum Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Novum Optimus</a> after they acquired <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a>. They remained a rather small nation until <a data-href="Ovus" href="remote-blog/characters/ovus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ovus</a> split The Egg and formed the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Bearer of the Egg" data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearers of the Egg</a>.Nation that it split into at some point<br>~4700 DA : <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Havus, The First Prodigy" data-href="Havus, The First Prodigy" href="remote-blog/characters/havus,-the-first-prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Havus</a> journeys the continent of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Navu > Medrum" data-href="Navu#Medrum" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html#Medrum" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Medrum</a> on the search for powerful mages.~4650 DA : Havus instructs some of the scholars in his party to investigate the sighting of a dragon that supposedly has kidnapped the weak and crippled people in the area.<br>~4645 DA : These scholars manage to meet with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Salgus, the Carrier" data-href="Salgus, the Carrier" href="remote-blog/characters/salgus,-the-carrier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Salgus</a> and a dispute breaks out ending with most of the scholars staying behind with Salgus whilst the others return to Havus.~4643 DA : Some of the scholars return to Havus and inform them that the dragon truly wishes to help people and that the others have stayed behind to study it. Havus instructs them to check up on them in some time but that the dragon was no longer his concern.~4640 DA : Some scholars head out to find Salgus in order to check up on the others that stayed behind.~4635 DA : The scholars find Salgus, commune with the scholars, and return to Havus. They tell of the great knowledge Salgus holds over their own kind. Havus wishes to meet the dragon.~4632 DA : Havus meets Salgus and they become close.<br>~4629 DA : Havus requests Salgus to inform him on the location of a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Dragons" data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragon</a> that could teach him how to use <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> more proficiently. Salgus eventually agrees and takes him to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Vokzan, the Prophet" data-href="Vokzan, the Prophet" href="remote-blog/characters/vokzan,-the-prophet.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vokzan</a> due to them being the only Chaos Dragon that Salgus readily knows and that may be willing to help.~4624 DA : Vokzan scoffs at Havus’ attempt to, in Vokzan’s words, “join the ranks of the dragons,” and as such decides to send Havus thousands of years into the future.~4623 DA : In honor of Havus, whom they believed dead, the remaining scholars and mages create a shrine in his honor and build a town around it, as many had no family to return to. This town would be known as Hava.<br>~4340 DA : Salgus visits a developed Hava and asks if scholars remain in their ranks. Upon confirmation, these scholars meet the preserved scholars within <a data-href="Salganoia" href="remote-blog/locations/salganoia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Salganoia</a>. The knowledge imparted on them sparks a renaissance in Hava focused upon scholarly matters.~4270 DA : Hava is visited by a neighboring kingdom and requests help in felling a dragon that has been harassing their kingdom as they have heard that the inhabitants of the town knew much of dragons. The residents of Hava decline leading to a slaughter being led on the village.~4269 DA : Survivors are either enslaved, run away to take up life elsewhere, or are still dedicated to their lifestyle and goals and decide to recreate Hava elsewhere.~4267 DA : A group of surviving mages and scholars of great influence and strength take refuge far away and begin to create a settlement dedicated to mages.~4266 DA : Groups venture out from this settlement to find promising mages, much like Havus had originally done over 400 years ago. However, instead of becoming an adventuring party, they all formed at this settlement now.~4237 DA : The settlement had gone by many names, but it was around this time that it had now been jokingly referred to as Magus Optimus as it was full of very powerful mages.~4186 DA : Across some generations, the name had transcended a mere joke and it became the name of what was now beginning to more so resemble a village of Mages that all now had kids and grandchildren that too were being taught the arcane.~3974 DA : Magus Optimus is officially recognized as a small nation.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/magus-optimus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Magus Optimus.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[List of All Things]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=".?query=tag:hidden" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#hidden">#hidden</a>
This is here to serve as a lookup table for things that exist and possibly when it was invented/discovered and who has possessed or learned or partaken in such things.]]></description><link>remote-blog/list-of-all-things.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/List of All Things.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fall of Scramloria]]></title><description><![CDATA[(111 DB).]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/fall-of-scramloria.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Fall of Scramloria.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Probot Massacre]]></title><description><![CDATA[(232 DB)
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a>, who had finally begun to feel comfort in their exertion of forces upon the world from their disembodied form, "possessed" an automaton of destruction made in <a data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthas</a> known as "Probot". It followed that, for the next 3 months, He Who Watches would utilize this device and its tools of mass destruction to lay waste to any evidence of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Humans" data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">human</a> life that he would come across. At the end, this automaton was destroyed.]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/probot-massacre.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Probot Massacre.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prodigy]]></title><description><![CDATA[The concentration of so many <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> into one spot (<a data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos</a>) caused <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy to behave a little strangely, causing <a data-href="Legyre" href="remote-blog/characters/legyre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Legyre</a> to create the cycle of the Prodigy. The Prodigy is to be able to harness <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> so as to keep its flow from going stagnant and clumping around Zataukeru too much.<br>This is a concept that Legyre had previously played around with before as a proof of concept with the creation of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Havus, The First Prodigy" data-href="Havus, The First Prodigy" href="remote-blog/characters/havus,-the-first-prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Havus</a>. It should be noted that, the creation of the prodigy then was unrelated to the flow of Chaos and Legyre simply wanted to have fun.Every 10 years after the prior Prodigy has died, Chaos energy will shoot away from Zataukeru and coalesce elsewhere into the formation of the Prodigy. ]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Prodigy.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chaos]]></title><description><![CDATA[A primordial form of energy that holds infinite power. Any reality can spontaneously erupt forth from this energy, and it is the embodiment of all creation, existence, and likelihood. It is with this energy that the first dragon, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragunthar, the First Dragon" data-href="Dragunthar, the First Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/dragunthar,-the-first-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragunthar</a>, was formed. Given that it was but a random occurrence, all of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a> do not look as you would expect a dragon to look necessarily, at least not at first. It wasn't until other horrors were born and fought each other that they began to wonder if they could increase their lethality. Rather than bashing their corporeal forms into each other, some dragons opted to tap into the Chaos surrounding them. Catching onto this, many of The First Dragons began to compete for finding a way to touch the Chaos. The first dragon to manage this connection to Chaos and utilize <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, albeit rather poorly, was <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon" data-href="Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/unavi,-the-enchanted-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unavi</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Chaos.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fusion of “Zode” (in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>) for performed (so like Zod-/Zo- for performer people or playful people) and “Lasciva” meaning playful in Latin.<br>Zosciva was one of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a> and was particularly keen on ‘roughhousing’ with the others by fighting them in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Magic" data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">magic</a>-less combat.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/zosciva,-the-flaming-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a>, whose name also means "Demon" in the <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>. She was the first dragon to utilize <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/unavi,-the-enchanted-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vokzan, the Prophet]]></title><description><![CDATA[“Vokzan” meaning ‘Future’ in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>.<br>Vokzan is a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Dragons" data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragon</a> one of the children of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon" data-href="Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/kupaulus,-the-hidden-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Kupaulus</a>. Vokzan took a great liking to the concept of weaker beings and loved to meddle in their affairs at their request by seeing how different their lives could turn out with foresight.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/vokzan,-the-prophet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Vokzan, the Prophet.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ulnigazi, the Lost Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fusion of “Ulnugazi” and “Ulkige” meaning ‘Hell’ and ‘Race’ in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a> respectively, leading to the name of ‘Hell Race’<br>Ulnigazi was the last of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a> and the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon</a> to decide to force particles of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> farther apart so that the spontaneous creation of more Dragons was no longer possible. Before the knowledge of how to use <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> was acquired, some formations were beginning to come along, so Ulnigazi ran away from the other First Dragons to systematically find and exterminate all life forms that were born ‘without his permission’.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/ulnigazi,-the-lost-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Ulnigazi, the Lost Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fusion of “Kupaudi” in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a> (meaning Caution) and “Solus” in Latin (meaning Alone).<br>Kupaulus was one of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a> who was deemed as a scaredy-cat and often bullied by <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> both born alongside them and after them. Out of such a deep desire of not being associated with the others, they chose to not conform their body to the acts of reproduction, thus making it so no descendants were ever formed via contraception from Kupaulus and instead were to be willingly made by their decision on few occasions. Kupaulus is also genderless as a result.<br>There are only a few cases of Kupaulus decided to make an offspring. These moments typically came in bouts of spite or loneliness and would serve as a distraction or tool of revenge. Kupaulus’ first child was <a data-href="Legyre" href="remote-blog/characters/legyre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Legyre</a>. Third child was <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Vokzan, the Prophet" data-href="Vokzan, the Prophet" href="remote-blog/characters/vokzan,-the-prophet.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vokzan</a>.Given the mostly solitary nature and the ‘punching bag’ role that Kupaulus often serves to other Dragons, they are not close with many others.<br>One of Kupaulus’ only friends among The First Dragons is <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Yeva, the Stable Dragon" data-href="Yeva, the Stable Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/yeva,-the-stable-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yeva</a> and they hold a deep hatred for <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon" data-href="Zosciva, the Flaming Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/zosciva,-the-flaming-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zosciva</a>. Kupaulus has had many conversations with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Grandun, the Great Dragon" data-href="Grandun, the Great Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grandun</a> before and they hold a respect towards each other for holding somewhat more solitary lifestyles, of course Grandun still is much more active with other Dragons and enjoys interacting with creatures of all types. <br>Kupaulus was the first creature to ever be killed, however death was not an extremely rigid concept at the time, and so it was more that the <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> holding Kupaulus in form was disrupted and a long time would need to pass before Kupaulus could interact with the world the same.<br>This death, which was accidentally (as The First Dragons did not yet know that anything akin to death could occur) caused by Zosciva was greatly devastating in concept to Yeva who created the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Concepts/Soul" data-href="Concepts/Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a> and gave structure to the Chaos that binds them allowing for death to not take so long to overcome.As an immediate consequence, Kupaulus was able to reform themselves together in a rather short amount of time.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/kupaulus,-the-hidden-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Kupaulus, the Hidden Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anomaly]]></title><description><![CDATA[A mystical anomaly found in the heart of <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a> that allows the energy of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> to neatly form the world sprouting out from it. It is likely that this was either an intended or unintended side effect of the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a> as it sort of acts like a huge knot between the strands of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magics/Magic" data-href="Magics/Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> that permeate outwards from it.It is debatable if the Anomaly is a physical object one could touch or if it is merely akin to a black hole but formed from dense fields of Magic that are untouchable by mortals.<br>Beings of great power born near the Anomaly are often so interwoven in its strands that they are tethered to either the immediate area or at least just the continent of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Navu > Medrum" data-href="Navu#Medrum" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html#Medrum" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Medrum</a>.<br>It is typical that things either born within some distance of the anomaly, or that spend much time in proximity to it, acquire stronger <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Affinity" data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinities</a> and other connections like that of the <a data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a> are usually strengthened too.]]></description><link>remote-blog/artifacts/anomaly.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Artifacts/Anomaly.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragunthar, the First Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a>]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/dragunthar,-the-first-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Dragunthar, the First Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Era of Prosperity]]></title><description><![CDATA[Immediately succeeding the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Humans" data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Human-kind</a>'s acquisition of <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a>, the Era of Prosperity began. It is in this sense we begin to see that those who care to record the history of the world from this point onwards is almost entirely composed of humans, as it was seen that no other race showed any signs of prosperity in this time. In a fate much akin to our own world, humans would rape the world of its resources with little concern of any adverse effects to come in the future. As more and more prowess over magic was attained, other lifeforms suffered more and more at the hands of human-kind's exploitation.<br>It was but only for a couple decades that humans were without a clue of how to exploit the dormant powers within <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a>, but eventually a mage came along who decided to shatter the egg into fragments so that its power could be broken into simpler pieces that were easier to take advantage of. This mage, <a data-href="Ovus" href="remote-blog/characters/ovus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ovus</a>, came to be the first <a data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearer of the Egg</a> as she took one of these fragments and began to distribute the remaining ones to other well-to-do mages. One of these mages, <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a>, came to grow discontent towards the way the world was advancing.<br>Before Xavier left, there was a roughly 3 year period where the nation that Ovus was from, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magus Optimus" data-href="Magus Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/magus-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magalo</a> reformed into <a data-href="Novum Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Novum Optimus</a> as the Bearers of the Egg took control as a council to lead the growing nation.<br>As a result, Xavier stole the current <a data-href="Prodigy" href="remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy</a> from the chambers they were held in in order to seal them away from the rest of the world permanently. This was because the others Bearers were speaking of using the Prodigy to open <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zataukeru</a> and bring about the <a data-href="Second Coming of the Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/concepts/second-coming-of-the-dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Second Coming of the Dragon Age</a>. To accomplish this goal of sealing them away, Xavier took the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy Child</a> to <a data-href="Dragonia" href="remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragonia</a> and performed a great spell at the <a data-href="Tower of the Eternal Eclipse" href="remote-blog/locations/tower-of-the-eternal-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tower of the Eternal Eclipse</a> alongside likeminded individuals of both great strength (<a data-href="Order of the Eclipse" href="remote-blog/factions/order-of-the-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Order of the Eclipse</a>) and of great weakness (Those who would come to inhabit this land). From that moment on, the lands of Dragonia were repurposed into <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>. The Prodigy Child, and all other members of the Order of the Eclipse, took refuge deep within <a data-href="Shadow's Peak" href="remote-blog/locations/shadow's-peak.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Shadow's Peak</a> where they were tasked with guarding the Prodigy.<br>For a long time, the nation of <a data-href="Novum Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Novum Optimus</a> took concern in losing one of the Bearers, but with no means of finding where Xavier had gone, they were left only with the option of putting up wanted posters and hoping for the best, and even that proved futile. Many years later, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Sintel, Keeper of Halüges" data-href="Sintel, Keeper of Halüges" href="remote-blog/characters/sintel,-keeper-of-halüges.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sintel</a> came across the emanating feeling of <a data-href="Draconic Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/draconic-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draconic Magic</a> from outside the barrier of Scramloria, and began to be suspicious of what lied within the random dome that had mysteriously appeared over Dragonia 32 years past. This emanating Draconic Magic was of course coming from <a data-href="Siethun" href="remote-blog/characters/siethun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Siethun</a> who resided within. As a result, Sintel raised this to the other Bearers of the Egg and received permission to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Fall of Scramloria" data-href="Fall of Scramloria" href="remote-blog/events/fall-of-scramloria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">siege</a> upon the dome barrier surrounding Scramloria to see what lies within, especially because its formation coincides with the time period Xavier had gone missing.<br>This of course led to the barrier weakening, allowing Sintel to slip in, battle Xavier, destroy the Tower of the Eternal Eclipse, cause mass panic, create bouts of <a data-href="Nightfall" href="remote-blog/concepts/nightfall.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nightfall</a>, kill Siethun, reveal the hiding place of the Prodigy Child, and then inevitably die to the hands of Xavier himself. Of course, it was too late for Scramloria, and all residents of the region-save <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gareth of Ishoria" data-href="Gareth of Ishoria" href="remote-blog/characters/gareth-of-ishoria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gareth</a>-perished from a mix of the armies and Nightfall. Additionally, the entire Order of the Eclipse was slain, and Xavier died as a sacrifice when performing the rite that accomplished the <a data-href="Prodigy's Disembodiment" href="remote-blog/events/prodigy's-disembodiment.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy's Disembodiment</a>. Of course, before doing so Xavier tied a small piece of his own essence to the Tower of the Eternal Eclipse's ruins.<br>Following the Fall of Scramloria, the Prodigy Child began to slowly gain control over the world even without a corporeal form, which was first manifested through whispering and feelings of being watched leading to the name He Who Watches being coined. This Age ends as soon as He Who Watches had gained enough power to perform the <a data-href="Probot Massacre" href="remote-blog/events/probot-massacre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Probot Massacre</a>, thus marking the descent of the world, and the end of the Era of Prosperity.The immediate year following the year the Formation of Draguia took place is recorded as 0 DB (Dragon-Bare). Every subsequent year adds 1 to this number.]]></description><link>remote-blog/ages/era-of-prosperity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Ages/Era of Prosperity.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Age of Fatigue]]></title><description><![CDATA[It is 232 DB. Many are dead as a result of the <a data-href="Probot Massacre" href="remote-blog/events/probot-massacre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Probot Massacre</a>, and <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> has been in use for about 204 years. The flow of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> is compromised and exhibits a polar nature. Due to all these facts, <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> begins to falter. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a> takes advantage of this fact, playing with those that survived his massacre. He banishes the remaining <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Bearer of the Egg" data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearers of the Egg</a> to <a data-href="Deisomnia" href="remote-blog/locations/deisomnia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Deisomnia</a> and fuses back together The Egg as a way to lure people. <a data-href="Novum Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Novum Optimus</a> as a result begins to fizzle out over the next 2 years as it struggles to form a strong government in a world where the force they are based in the study of, Magic, is turning increasingly weak and obsolete. On another note, with the promise of great power were one to obtain The Egg, He Who Watches began to gain excitement from watching people fight over it and compete for resources, technology, land, and artifacts. Examples of how the entire world was now aware of The Egg can be seen with groups of <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> that partook in the actions of things like the <a data-href="1st SMP" href="remote-blog/smps/1st-smp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">1st SMP</a> and <a data-href="2nd SMP" href="remote-blog/smps/2nd-smp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">2nd SMP</a>. Those examples didn't go too crazy, so He Who Watches will not have cared, but there were also cases where people really fell for his game and became his source of entertainment. One example of this is the events of the <a data-href="3rd SMP" href="remote-blog/smps/3rd-smp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">3rd SMP</a>. After around 16 years of He Who Watches playing this game however, <a data-href="Gareth of Ishoria" href="remote-blog/characters/gareth-of-ishoria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gareth of Ishoria</a> would return to the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ruins of Scramloria</a> and his activity would bring about <a data-href="His Weakening" href="remote-blog/events/his-weakening.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">His Weakening</a>. In this period of time, He Who Watches gets angry and tries to find Gareth, but finds his efforts barred due to a mysterious power coming from the destroyed <a data-href="Tower of the Eternal Eclipse" href="remote-blog/locations/tower-of-the-eternal-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tower of the Eternal Eclipse</a>. This force, of course, was the spirit of <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a> that he had tied to the ruined landmark before dying. In the mean time, Magic starts to come back somewhat as it has been sometime since The Egg was used in its fractured form to abuse its power, though it is still much weaker than it once was. During this time, the <a data-href="4th SMP" href="remote-blog/smps/4th-smp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">4th SMP</a> would also take place. With He Who Watches now at his weakest, he begins to get desperate, and starts to make small influences all over the world in hopes of creating <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Followers of He" data-href="Followers of He" href="remote-blog/factions/followers-of-he.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">zealots</a> ambitious enough to come and boost his power either through some form of <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> or by stopping Gareth.It is at this point that the story of the final SMP will take place.<br>The same year system as the <a data-href="Era of Prosperity" href="remote-blog/ages/era-of-prosperity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Era of Prosperity</a> is used (DB).]]></description><link>remote-blog/ages/age-of-fatigue.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Ages/Age of Fatigue.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Age of Chaos]]></title><description><![CDATA[At the beginning of time-no, even before that-there was <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a>. From this Chaos erupted <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a>. Eventually, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon" data-href="Unavi, the Enchanted Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/unavi,-the-enchanted-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unavi</a> managed to tap into the powers of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, which developed into an art that was necessary to master for any dragons or else they would suffer death at the hands of another. These powerful <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> only grew more and more powerful as they procreated, as it takes Chaos to form a dragon, and some of the Chaos of the parents would be inherited into the offspring, creating a positive feedback loop. As these dragons became more and more dense with Chaos, they were able to better control the unpredictable nature of Chaos Magic, however, this caused them to generally be weaker in return with what they could manage in these controlled situations. As a solution, a dragon known as <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a> performed an incredibly powerful spell with Chaos Magic that caused the energies of chaos to condense into a variety of different weaker energies that weaved together to create <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> in an event known as the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>. This, of course, was only able to be done due to Aternos' increased Chaos Magic control, and the massacre of 20% of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon-kind</a>. This massacre was done so that Aternos had enough Chaos energy to actually perform the giant spell that was the Unification of Magic. Once Chaos was split into threads and weaved into the fluid and malleable energy of Magic, the Age of Chaos came to a close.The last year of the Age of Chaos is 0 Cs (Meaning Chaos). Going closer to the dawn of time increases it by 1 for every year./]]></description><link>remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Ages/Age of Chaos.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:15:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Firelash]]></title><description><![CDATA[Firelash is a <a data-href="Homunculus" href="remote-blog/races/homunculus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Homunculus</a> created by <a data-href="Yunem" href="remote-blog/characters/yunem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yunem</a> with the purpose of being able to always identify Yunem regardless of the inhabited body and formed <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Soul" data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">soul</a>. He utilizes a device attached to his head that acts a conduit for <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magic > Vessel-Bound Magic" data-href="Magic#Vessel-Bound Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html#Vessel-Bound Magic" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vessel-Bound Magic</a> to channel the artificial <a data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinity</a> for fire that makes up his body.<br>For his creation, his body wasn't physically augmented to anything beyond the capabilities of a normal <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Humans" data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">human</a>. That being said, the belly that Firelash has is extremely armored and can even be made into an incredibly bouncy surface at the will of Firelash, allowing more versatility and defense there than that of a normal human.<br>There were some kinks in his initial memories that <a data-href="Yunem" href="remote-blog/characters/yunem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Yunem</a> didn't have time to work out due to an attack launched by the <a data-href="Syndicate of Wraiths" href="remote-blog/factions/syndicate-of-wraiths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Syndicate of Wraiths</a> upon the village he was staying in. As such, Firelash is a generally more hot-headed and self-absorbed creature that tends to believe his fire <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> is truly his own and isn't reliant on the technology adorned to his body. The only reason he doesn't attempt to test his theory is that he thinks its sick to have fire for hair and come out of his head so he just keeps his status quo that he seems to love too much to abandon.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/firelash.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Firelash.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Diary of Yunem]]></title><description><![CDATA[254 (DB) Granda 9th,
The stampede of horses was heard over the horizon. "They're here," I thought. Perhaps this is no time to act as if my life is some story book though, for the <a data-href="Syndicate of Wraiths" href="remote-blog/factions/syndicate-of-wraiths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Syndicate of Wraiths</a> is upon us. We frantically took to weaponry, but <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Wraiths" data-href="Wraiths" href="remote-blog/races/wraiths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">wraiths</a> are no ordinary creatures. To damage a wraith, one must use some form <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> or some form of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Enchanting" data-href="Enchanting" href="remote-blog/magics/enchanting.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">magically augmented weaponry</a>. I have been in the works on a <a data-href="Homunculus" href="remote-blog/races/homunculus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Homunculus</a> for quite some time now, but I fear they are not yet ready for the world. I'd like to tweak some of their memories, you see. I fear that if I released them now they may turn out a little more hot-headed then I'd like for a future companion. Ever since I discovered I had a cycle of rebirth due to my <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Tho-Dragun" data-href="Tho-Dragun" href="remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">lineage</a> I have desired to make a creature capable of identifying me regardless of my possession of a new <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Soul" data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">soul</a> and form and to remind me of who I truly am. I suppose I don't have much a choice however, so I suppose today I unveil him. My fire-slinging dad-bod of awesomeness and eternal stability-<a data-href="Firelash" href="remote-blog/characters/firelash.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Firelash</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/stories/diary-of-yunem.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Stories/Diary of Yunem.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:09:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Calendar System]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=".?query=tag:hidden" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#hidden">#hidden</a> 1 - ...... : Named after
2 - ...... : Named after<br>
3 - Granda: Named after <a data-href="Grandun, The Great Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grandun, The Great Dragon</a>
4 - ...... : Named after
..
..
..]]></description><link>remote-blog/calendar-system.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Calendar System.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:08:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yunem]]></title><description><![CDATA[Originally a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dragon</a> who lived up to just before the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> where they decided they did not wish to leave <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a>. This prompted them to attempt refuge with <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a>, however they turned on Yunem and attempted to murder him. Yunem attempted to sacrifice himself in order to retaliate and finally move on, but the circumstances caused a disturbance that saw Yunem awaking 100 hundred years later. In this form, he was known as Thonem once he learned of his previous life as a dragon. They were somewhat angry that they had amnesia over their rebirth, and attempted to seek out a method of connecting their memories once again. In their efforts, Thonem was attacked after only 38 years of living by a group of bandits and ended up losing their life in the process. Thonem then was reborn as Kahrin around another 100 years later, and it was in this life that they successfully learned of their previous identities, and even obtained the memories. He changed his name to Yunem once again after only 19 years, and began to dedicate himself to the creation of <a data-href="Firelash" href="remote-blog/characters/firelash.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Firelash</a> in hopes that they would be able to restore memories and purpose to him if Yunem ever does die and once again rebirth.<br>In the modern day, Yunem is a <a data-href="Tho-Dragun" href="remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tho-Dragun</a> mage and alchemist with the goal of establishing longevity in their identity.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/yunem.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Yunem.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Soul]]></title><description><![CDATA[On the creation of a lifeform, around the same time <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> is collapsing into an <a data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinity</a>, a metaphysical object is formed that acts as a sort of gravitational prison for the <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> a creature possesses called a soul. It isn't necessarily gravity, but the magic of a person is bound by some barrier that the soul forms. As magic is the fundamental force that forms all beings, a soul being it's bounding force makes it a rather fundamental part of your identity. Furthermore, when the soul is separated from the body, magic tends to form a stretched hourglass shape having a bulb where the soul is and where the body is. With this, one can technically extend the control of their most potent magic past just the bounds of their soul, but it can place the user at a great risk. If the magic lingering between the soul and body is severed by any manner, the soul cannot return to its body and enters a purgatory-like state where it can roam the world freely but only for as long as the magic it contains hasn't burnt out due to no organic systems refreshing it. If this process completes, a soul is transported to <a data-href="Surturins" href="remote-blog/locations/surturins.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Surturins</a> (however one can opt in to going there early), otherwise, one can become something like a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Wraiths > Enwraiths" data-href="Wraiths#Enwraiths" href="remote-blog/races/wraiths.html#Enwraiths" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Enwraith</a> in order to sustain themselves and remain in <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/soul.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Soul.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Homunculus]]></title><description><![CDATA[An <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Alchemy" data-href="Alchemy" href="remote-blog/magics/alchemy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">alchemical</a> creature forged as a synthetic life-form. They are not necessarily always aware of this fact that they have been made, as memories are able to be forged upon their birth. Homunculi typically struggle with having a properly formed <a data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinity</a> as the process with which the homunculus was brought into being is different from a typical creature's birth. As such, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magic > Vessel-Bound Magic" data-href="Magic#Vessel-Bound Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html#Vessel-Bound Magic" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">apparatuses</a> are typically used to allow such creatures access to magic. Otherwise, homunculi can often be gifted with greater strength allowing them a chance in combat even without explicit access to magic. It should be noted that homunculi do not typically possess a <a data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a> unless otherwise fused with them, such as the practice of trying to revive someone through creating them a new body.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/homunculus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Homunculus.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wraiths]]></title><description><![CDATA[Enwraiths were not Wraiths by birth, but rather through a ritual in where a <a data-href="Soul" href="remote-blog/concepts/soul.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Soul</a> can mimic most properties of a wraith in following their practices, such as siphoning other souls for energy.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/wraiths.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Wraiths.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:26:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[The purest form of controlled magics, being the careful weaving of many threads of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> into a pure source of magic with easy usage. The weaves interlocked in different manners, allowing for different forms of magic to take root by varying the amounts of which thread clusters you used from the pure magic form.<br>One manner through which magic can be channeled is by using a scientific device to allow those with more difficulty in using magic to be able to take advantage of whatever lies within them, typically their <a data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinity</a>. This magic is a type of support that allows the magic of the wearer to take fruition, and often means their magic can only be as strong as the device through which it is channeled by. There is also the added weakness that you are no longer able to utilize this magic if the device is harmed or can no longer run.]]></description><link>remote-blog/magics/magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Magics/Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:13:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></title><link>remote-blog/magics/alchemy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Magics/Alchemy.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:05:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Enchanting]]></title><link>remote-blog/magics/enchanting.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Magics/Enchanting.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:03:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Syndicate of Wraiths]]></title><description><![CDATA[A grouping of wraiths dedicated to a strategic gaining of control over human villages, cities, and nations in order to assert power and dominion within the world to establish themselves as something other than a creature lesser than what humans are capable of.]]></description><link>remote-blog/factions/syndicate-of-wraiths.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/Syndicate of Wraiths.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ovus]]></title><description><![CDATA[She/herAn accomplished mage and the first <a data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearer of the Egg</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/ovus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Ovus.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arthas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mechanical city inhabited originally by <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon</a>-worshipping <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> who were graced by the presence of <a data-href="Grandun, The Great Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grandun, The Great Dragon</a>. Grandun allowed the Humans to partake in an <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> with him leading to the creation of <a data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiods</a>.<br>~2400 DA : Arthas is formed by a group of scholars who had been banished from their homeland, <a data-href="Magus Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/magus-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magus Optimus</a>, with the goal of using machinery and <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> together in perfect unison.~2300 DA : Arthas is attacked by Magus Optimus and is left in ruin as the remaining people are left to pick up the scraps, massively slowing down the speed of progression.~1900 DA : Grandun visits the lands of Arthas in his gear-like form, inspiring Arthans to utilize such designs for their benefits.~1850 DA : Grandun visits once again, this time sleeping and protecting Arthas by coiling his body around it. Grandun enters a great slumber while Arthans begin to inspect his body.~1700 DA : Several complex designs had already been made and put to use, but it is at this time that construction of a prototype Artificiod completes, however they find no way to power it, and begin to analyze the Magics that make up Grandun.<br>~1630 DA : Grandun completes a nearly 220 year slumber as he wakes to the sight of Arthas having advanced greatly. It is at this time that Grandun makes an Oath with the people of Arthas, and the first Artificiod, <a data-href="Artho" href="remote-blog/characters/artho.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artho</a>, is made.~1600 DA : Grandun departs from Arthas, having changed material designs many times during his slumber, and left in a glimmering glass form.~1400 DA : The Artificiod is perfected and a civil war begins as they make claim to hold rights.~1390 DA : The Artificiods win and are recognized as fully sapient beings by the people of Arthas. However, the rights of Artificiods are still of great debate.~1300 DA : Artificiods hold equal rights to that of Humans.~800 DA : Artificiods begin to out populate Humans.~740 DA : As the numbers of Humans dwindle, they begin to lose their rights within Arthas.~710 DA : After many mini-skirmishes and outrages, Humans are fully stripped of their rights and viewed as lesser than by Artificiods.~680 DA : After 30 years of being used as slaves and for experiments, the Human Exclusion Act is passed and all Humans are either to be outcast or slain.~665 DA : The last Human dies within Arthas. Arthas is exclusively inhabited by Artificiods now, and they are incredibly Xenophobic to all species deemed to have "less intelligence." The only exception is that of Dragons, of course Artificiods still consider themselves superior to most dragons.~630 DA : To prove their superiority, and to advance their magic, Artificiods begin to design devices to kill Dragons with.<br>~350 DA : The <a data-href="Chaos Backprocessor" href="remote-blog/artifacts/chaos-backprocessor.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Backprocessor</a> is invented by the Artificiods.<br>~330 DA : As both a proof of concept and for the future of Magical development, the Artificiods use the Chaos Backprocessor and fell a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Dragons" data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragon</a>, albeit one of the youngest ones.~327 DA : The land of Arthas is entirely decimated by several Chaos Dragons. Only that which was underground survived.~190 DA : Arthas finishes developing a new sprawling underground city, and has entirely hidden their presence from the surface.~87 DA : Arthas begins production of automatons in hopes of creating one that can take advantage of a Chaos Backprocessor.0 DB : Artho is re-activated after being excavated from their deep burial site.7 DB : Artho volunteers for a new program to construct humanoid appearing Artificiods for infiltrating Human societies.9 DB : Artho is disguised as a sort of Human, despite still being an Artificiod, and is given several upgrades to their dated design.<br>23 DB : A search party of several Human-disguised Artificiods discover that the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> had occurred and that <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> exists.24 DB : Secret development on a way to harvest The Egg's power begins.28 DB : Arthans figure out how to harvest The Egg's power, so they send out Artho once again to find it.29 DB : Artho learns that The Egg has been shattered.31 DB : Artificiods begin work on AI's that do not operate off of physical form like they do.45 DB : Arthans begin to work on their final model of automaton.92 DB : The shell of the final automaton is completed, and now the installation of the Chaos Backprocessor begins.98 DB : The Chaos Backprocessor is installed, but the automaton is not finished until they give it a proper conscientiousness model.119 DB : The method of housing a non-corporeal intelligence is completed by utilizing Chaos energy.123 DB : The final automaton, Probot, is finished as it is installed with a non-corporeal intelligence.134 DB : Development of a super AI begins.<br>178 DB : The super AI, <a data-href="NAHFL" href="remote-blog/characters/nahfl.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">NAHFL</a>, is completed.<br>203 DB : <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a> possesses the final automaton Probot and the Artificiods realize this and ask the goal of the pseudo-God. When He Who Watches says he intends to kill all living creatures that stand before him, the Artificiods say he is welcome to do so, as they have far surpassed such lowly creatures nearly a millennia ago and could care less what happens to them. The <a data-href="Probot Massacre" href="remote-blog/events/probot-massacre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Probot Massacre</a> commences.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/arthas.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Arthas.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:58:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Proto-Humans]]></title><description><![CDATA[The predecessor to <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> that existed up until at least 2000 years before the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/proto-humans.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Proto-Humans.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 03:57:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Surturins]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=".?query=tag:via" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#via">#via</a>
"its like a pit of acid that a soul walks into that sort of burns away memory"
"Aivener maintains the pits and lends the byproducts to other branches of the spiritual realm"
"its like a brine processing plant but instead of brine its souls"
"you choose to go there, like donating your body to science but spiritual""a sort of cyclical purgatory that turns the newly dead into the to-be born""probably other people like technicians and business heads""maybe souls are a limited resource, so maybe the surturins is a way to sell souls to unborn vessels""maybe without it, you have a 5% chance of your child being born without a soul""maybe soul classism"]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/surturins.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Surturins.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 07:29:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aivener]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=".?query=tag:via" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#via">#via</a>
full name: Aivener kshev s'remtier<br>
she is a <a data-href="Tho-Dragun" href="remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tho-Dragun</a><br>
daughter of Kshev (<a data-href="Inkiab" href="remote-blog/characters/inkiab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Inkiab</a>) of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Lineage" data-href="#Lineage" href="#Lineage" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lineage of Arem (s'Remtier)</a><br>
Stewardess of <a data-href="Surturins" href="remote-blog/locations/surturins.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Surturins</a>.<br>The s'Remtier line goes back to the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>. <a data-href="Arem" href="remote-blog/characters/arem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arem</a> was a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dragon</a> that in fear of being eradicated as a part of the 20% of dragons who died, was forced to quantum-hibernate and eons later reawake as a human. but a human who cannot die in the traditional sense. For example, Tharem (Human Arem/Broken Arem in dragon-language) lived 500 years laying low until they got fatally injured when a village got invaded in a war. Tharem didnt just end, but mutated into Inkiab ("second born son" in a human language where Tharem died). Almost a mellenium later, Inkiab gave way to Aivener who later establishes the Surturins. She was able to do this because everytime a broken dragon-human mutates upon death, the new being gains a small reserve of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> that is a fraction of the original Arem's magic. This magic is what Aivener used to create the system by which <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> can elect to send their souls to her for the Surturins.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/aivener.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Aivener.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 06:11:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salgus, the Carrier]]></title><description><![CDATA[Similar to the Latin of “salus” for “salvation.” A rather powerful <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon</a> born after the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>. He had a propensity to harbor <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> and other lesser races within his <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Salganoia" data-href="Salganoia" href="remote-blog/locations/salganoia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">pocket dimension</a>. It is very irregular for any <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> using creatures to be able to create pocket dimensions without the aid of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, however Salgus was still able to manage so through having all <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Affinity" data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">affinities</a> and a great portion of Magic.<br>Salgus did not care much for the affairs of the world and the ongoing war against his kind during the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a> and instead opted to either stay within his pocket dimension or to recruit others to join him within. These people that accompanied him were allowed to exit at any time, and it was treated as a reprieve from the world outside. Furthermore, those that wished to carry out diplomatic relations often opted to do so within Salganoia if they could, as it was protected entirely under the rule of a Dragon. Countless artifacts deemed too dangerous were often stolen or brought before the pocket dimension to be stored away from those with a heart full of wrath. There were even many cases of Dragon Historians opting to never leave the pocket dimension and instead remain in contact with Salgus.<br>Those with access to Chaos Magic can brute force their way into Salganoia, and with great effort most with all affinities could likely replicate these results, albeit with much more difficulty. The only case of someone brute forcing their way in was <a data-href="Havus, The First Prodigy" href="remote-blog/characters/havus,-the-first-prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Havus, The First Prodigy</a>, and this was only due to the knowledge of the location of <a data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos</a> being known by the scholars within. This action, of course, weakened the original spell and thus it now holds an incompleteness such that upon the death of Salgus, the pocket dimension will flood out from their corpse and desecrate the nearby land.<br>Salgus, during the <a data-href="Era of Prosperity" href="remote-blog/ages/era-of-prosperity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Era of Prosperity</a>, often chose to hide away as he saw it mostly obsolete to ask of people to run from their world now that it was seemingly much better off. This doesn’t mean he never explored though, and eventually he ran into <a data-href="Grandun, The Great Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grandun, The Great Dragon</a>, who commemorated Salgus’ capabilities even as a lesser Dragon, and offered an <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> to increase his power, to which Salgus turned down. Instead, Grandun mentioned a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Arthas" data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">society</a> that he had seen flourish over a millennia ago. He told Salgus that there may exist Humans there that would interest him due to their vast intellect. When Salgus visited the area Grandun told him about however, he found nothing but a barren plains. There was, however, one lone <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Artificiods" data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiod</a> named <a data-href="Jexus" href="remote-blog/characters/jexus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Jexus</a> that had been attempting to run from his people, but was scared of what may become of him. As a result, Jexus agreed to enter Salgus’ pocket dimension, despite being unsure of if even that was a safe option.<br>As time went on, and it became the <a data-href="Age of Fatigue" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-fatigue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Fatigue</a>, Salgus often visited the world less, of which he felt guilty. He wanted to visit and offer the world that seemed to need it the most, but he was scared of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a>. After having to deal with Havus, he did not want to summon the wrath of an even more powerful <a data-href="Prodigy" href="remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy</a>. As a result, Salgus is very interested in methods of permanently destroying the Prodigy Cycle, believing it to be unnecessary in maintaining the flow of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> when <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> already seemed to create more than enough flow previously.<br>Jexus and the Dragon Scholars within Salganoia often work together now making requests to Salgus to allow them out at certain locations for brief periods of time to learn more of how to combat He Who Watches. Upon learning of <a data-href="His Weakening" href="remote-blog/events/his-weakening.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">His Weakening</a>, Salgus went to visit <a data-href="Gareth of Ishoria" href="remote-blog/characters/gareth-of-ishoria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gareth of Ishoria</a> and now plans to provide him with the proper resources and power that he may need to move forwards. They have also considered creating an Oath with one another, however they would require an artifact to properly channel the Magic of the Oath due to Gareth’s late-stage <a data-href="Magic Sickness" href="remote-blog/concepts/magic-sickness.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic Sickness</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/salgus,-the-carrier.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Salgus, the Carrier.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:56:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artificiods]]></title><description><![CDATA[Artificial men constructed by the <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> of <a data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthas</a>. They are powered under the placement of an <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> connecting to the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Grandun, The Great Dragon" data-href="Grandun, The Great Dragon" href="remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Great Dragon, Grandun</a>.<br>They are an incredibly xenophobic race of creatures, and they firmly believe in their intellectual superiority to all other living creatures. As such, they often won't hesitate to demonstrate their superiority in other manners that they see fit, such as felling a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Dragons" data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragon</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/artificiods.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Artificiods.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Helga, The Elder Goddess]]></title><description><![CDATA[Earliest Goddess within <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a>, additionally known as the "Sower of Madness." Before the end of the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a>, she fed off the results of failed use of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a>, and stowed infighting amongst creatures which could wield it in order to create more sources to feed from.<br>With the end of the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a>, Helga split into 5 separate Goddess', known as the Daughters of The Elder. This was due to the fact that she simply couldn't incite as much misuse of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> that was needed to keep her sustained as one whole. ]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/helga,-the-elder-goddess.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Helga, The Elder Goddess.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adreil]]></title><description><![CDATA[Goddess of Adventure within <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>. Highly responsible for the number of adventurer's and explorer's within <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>, as she has provided visions of great battles and treasure to be found in the area to outsiders. Additionally responsible for the many danger's present with the area, as she pushed many particularly savage creatures to the land, as well as many of the last remaining <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a>.<br>4th Daughter of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Helga, The Elder Goddess" data-href="Helga, The Elder Goddess" href="remote-blog/characters/helga,-the-elder-goddess.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Elder</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/adreil.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Adreil.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jexus]]></title><description><![CDATA[A rogue <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Artificiods" data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiod</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/jexus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Jexus.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salganoia]]></title><link>remote-blog/locations/salganoia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Salganoia.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Havus, The First Prodigy]]></title><link>remote-blog/characters/havus,-the-first-prodigy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Havus, The First Prodigy.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 03:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3rd SMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[There was a huge tech mod focus by a majority of the players that got powerful. Additionally, this was the longest lasting of any of the 4 SMPs that have been done. There were many mod changes made throughout its run time, and small bouts of admin abuse. Many of the bases were found along a river that ran from the ocean to a forest and into a mesa. Some others were located on the middle of the ocean and on a plateau in the mountains. There was also a base far away on a mushroom island. There was no real gimmick but there were attempts at lore and roleplay. Specifically, when the egg was obtained it was the goal of some other members to obtain it for themselves.
(Done around November 23rd 2022 up till around sometime after March 22nd 2023 with evidence of it having been played on as late as May 29th 2023)Example of how crazy involved I was in the tech aspect with the river and its cliff face in the background.
<img alt="Low Quality Photo of 3rd SMP.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/low-quality-photo-of-3rd-smp.webp" target="_self"><br>This was a successful group of <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> that actually had acquired <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> for themselves. Not only that, but there was significant restoration of infrastructure and technology within the area that this took place in. If it weren't for the nuclear explosions and reactor breakdowns in the area, this could have eventually grown into a well-to-do establishment of humanity. This was the most appeasing course of events for <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a> to watch.]]></description><link>remote-blog/smps/3rd-smp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/SMPs/3rd SMP.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:22:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2nd SMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[This SMP was similar to the 1st in the sense that it did not conclude at any late game point. The dragon egg was not obtained, and mostly only overworld progress was made. Similar to the first time, there were factions, but this time mostly only 2-3. There was also a lore document dating back to this point in time, however its lore focuses on more than just dragons being the original species and implies some things ruled different parts of the world with the dragon just happening to be the strongest of them. Here is an attached map that was made during the time we must have played:
(Done around May 8th 2022)<img alt="Map Of Second SMP.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/map-of-second-smp.webp" target="_self">There were also some custom recipes:<br>
<img alt="Reinforced Oak Planks Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/reinforced-oak-planks-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Reinforced Wooden Axe Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/reinforced-wooden-axe-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Diamond Battle Axe Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/diamond-battle-axe-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Silk Touch Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/silk-touch-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Diamond Greatsword Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/diamond-greatsword-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Emblem of Resistance Tier I Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/emblem-of-resistance-tier-i-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Emblem of Resistance Tier II Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/emblem-of-resistance-tier-ii-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Wooden Dagger Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/wooden-dagger-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>For the sake of current lore, we will now consider this in much the same way we consider the first. This was just a group of <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> who had heard some legends of <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> but in the end were more concerned about their own lives and building their relations and nations than partaking in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a>' game. This is yet another side story.]]></description><link>remote-blog/smps/2nd-smp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/SMPs/2nd SMP.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:06:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1st SMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[In the 1st SMP done under the Scrambled SMP, the lore was a little different given that it said Dragons terrorized people and pillagers fought back sending them to the End. However, in this iteration the egg was still meant to be a source of power, this will be how it is adapted into our current lore. This was non-modded and we each chose faction names to operate our bases from. There was also supposedly a gimmick on the server being: "The dragon egg could be turned to shards that made things Unbreakable."
(Done around December 4th 2021)There were also many custom recipes:
<img alt="Empty Spawner Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/empty-spawner-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Zombie Spawn Egg Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/zombie-spawn-egg-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Saddle Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/saddle-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Iron Horse Armor Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/iron-horse-armor-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Curse of Vanishing Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/curse-of-vanishing-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Curse of Binding Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/curse-of-binding-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Dragon Soul Shard Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/dragon-soul-shard-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Dragon Egg Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/dragon-egg-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Dragon-Infused Weapon Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/dragon-infused-weapon-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Dragon Soul Shard from Dragon-Infused Weapon Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/dragon-soul-shard-from-dragon-infused-weapon-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Chainmail Helmet Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/chainmail-helmet-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Enchanted Golden Apple Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/enchanted-golden-apple-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Iron-Plated Shield Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/iron-plated-shield-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Gold-Plated Shield Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/gold-plated-shield-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>
<img alt="Diamond-Plated Shield Recipe.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/diamond-plated-shield-recipe.webp" target="_self"><br>We will consider the events of the 1st SMP as an area of the world where there was a group of <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> curious about <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a>. However, as I don't recall it ever even getting close to obtaining the egg, these people will have eventually grown tired of their goal and have given up. This means the events of the 1st SMP were more akin to a side story, with slight progress being made, but overall the Humans did not succumb to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a>' games.]]></description><link>remote-blog/smps/1st-smp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/SMPs/1st SMP.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:02:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Humans]]></title><description><![CDATA[The evolution of <a data-href="Proto-Humans" href="remote-blog/races/proto-humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Proto-Humans</a>. They are responsible for many of the actions taken against <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> as their prowess over technology and a unique mix between it and <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> has led to their fast development as a species.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/humans.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Humans.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aternos]]></title><description><![CDATA[The <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon</a> accountable for the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a> after slaughtering of 20% of dragon-kind. He also performed the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> spell as an apology to those he killed during the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a> and to separate the advancing lives of <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> from the fully evolved life of <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/aternos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Aternos.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unification of Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[Performed by <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a> during the end of the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a> to fix the unpredictable nature of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> by forming <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a>. It is in general the most powerful spell that is currently active in the universe, and likely the most powerful to have ever been or to ever be performed. Of course, it required the <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy of about 20% of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon-kind</a> which was achieved through their mass slaughtering by Aternos.]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Unification of Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Draguia]]></title><description><![CDATA[The pocket dimension realm contained within <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a>' bones following the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> at the end of the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a>. A majority of all <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> live within Draguia.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/draguia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Draguia.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chaos Dragons]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> that were born before the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a> and are capable of using <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>. Most Chaos Dragons live in <a data-href="Draguia" href="remote-blog/locations/draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draguia</a> following the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a> by <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a>, the most powerful of Chaos Dragons.]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Chaos Dragons.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zatau meaning "Immortal" and Keru meaning "Shrine" in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>. It can only be accessed through usage of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> and houses <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a>. Within Aternos' bones is the pocket dimension realm of <a data-href="Draguia" href="remote-blog/locations/draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draguia</a> that most <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> inhabit.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gareth of Ishoria]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gareth was born in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a> and became the Lord of <a data-href="Ishoria" href="remote-blog/locations/ishoria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ishoria</a> due to his freakish power.<br>He was about 23 when the <a data-href="Fall of Scramloria" href="remote-blog/events/fall-of-scramloria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Fall of Scramloria</a> occurred. Most who suffered from the effects of <a data-href="Nightfall" href="remote-blog/concepts/nightfall.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nightfall</a> perished, but Gareth was strong enough to actually survive and, though he had <a data-href="Magic Sickness" href="remote-blog/concepts/magic-sickness.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic Sickness</a>, he was able to gain <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Magic" data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magical capabilities</a>.<br>After the Fall of Scramloria, he spent about 137 years doing other things learning about the circumstances leading to the death of everyone he had ever known and how to defeat <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Remains</a> before returning to the ruins of Scramloria and using his knowledge to cause <a data-href="His Weakening" href="remote-blog/events/his-weakening.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">His Weakening</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/gareth-of-ishoria.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Gareth of Ishoria.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Magic Sickness]]></title><link>remote-blog/concepts/magic-sickness.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Magic Sickness.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:42:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[4th SMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[This SMP was very involved on the side of having gimmicks. This is the first one to feature something as changing as a magic mod, and it revolved heavily around that when referring to its gimmicks. All of these changes are shown below:<img alt="Mox's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/mox's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Chillest's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/chillest's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Destroyer's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/destroyer's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Link's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/link's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Orange's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/orange's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Rain's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/rain's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Blu's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/blu's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Glitch's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/glitch's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Game's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/game's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Vebe's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/vebe's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Duckebo's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/duckebo's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Purple's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/purple's-sheet.webp" target="_self"><img alt="Poke's Sheet.webp" src="remote-blog/smps/poke's-sheet.webp" target="_self">These gimmicks were paired with only being able to form teams of players with the following ruling:Point Values (10 points max on a team):
7 - Ali
6 - Ryken
5 - Ryker
4 - Skyler
4 - Blu
3 - Kai
3 - Aidan
3 - Isaac
3 - Chase
2 - Kiley
2 - Via
2 - Game
2 - KianThese values were based off a combo of knowing tech mods, being good at pvp, and just being good at minecraft in general.<br>Much like all the other times that <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> were tempted by <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a>, but this happened as <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> was coming back. Many <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> were fostered by these Humans too, but The Egg was still not acquired by this group, making it more of a side story.]]></description><link>remote-blog/smps/4th-smp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/SMPs/4th SMP.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:36:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Followers of He]]></title><description><![CDATA[Those that follow <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a> and, in the <a data-href="Age of Fatigue" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-fatigue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Fatigue</a>, are encouraged by him to provide himself with strength or to kill his oppressors.]]></description><link>remote-blog/factions/followers-of-he.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/Followers of He.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragon Zealots]]></title><description><![CDATA[People that believe in the <a data-href="Second Coming of the Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/concepts/second-coming-of-the-dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Second Coming of the Dragon Age</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/factions/dragon-zealots.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/Dragon Zealots.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bearer of the Egg]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mostly composed of <a data-href="Dragon Zealots" href="remote-blog/factions/dragon-zealots.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Zealots</a>, the Bearers of the Egg were those who held a fragment of <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> and thus had heightened power.]]></description><link>remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/Bearer of the Egg.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:27:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Second Coming of the Dragon Age]]></title><description><![CDATA[Many <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragon Zealots" data-href="Dragon Zealots" href="remote-blog/factions/dragon-zealots.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">people</a> believe in re-instating an effect closer to the early days of the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a> wherein <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> are once again let to roam free and would then be allotted more <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> for birth than <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a>, thus restoring the Dragons' former glory. This goal would be accomplished by utilizing someone who can perform uses of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, like the <a data-href="Prodigy" href="remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy</a>, and then opening the seal to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zataukeru</a>. ]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/second-coming-of-the-dragon-age.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Second Coming of the Dragon Age.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:26:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ishoria]]></title><description><![CDATA[Part of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a> and was a city built entirely upon the water.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/ishoria.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Ishoria.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:16:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragus]]></title><description><![CDATA[Part of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a> and the original capital of the nation of <a data-href="Dragonia" href="remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragonia</a>.
scramloria* lore hereyap yap yap]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/dragus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Dragus.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 23:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Main Timeline]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a href=".?query=tag:hidden" class="tag is-unresolved" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow" data-href="#hidden">#hidden</a>
Brief Overview:<br>
Everything will start with the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a> and advance into the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a> after <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a>' <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>. In the Dragon Age, <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> fought against the <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> to gain more magical prowess. At the end of this war, Aternos sacrificed themselves to create a parallel reality known as <a data-href="Draguia" href="remote-blog/locations/draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draguia</a> housed entirely within <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos' grave</a>. Aternos created a seal around the tomb that required <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a> to open, making only the <a data-href="Prodigy" href="remote-blog/concepts/prodigy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy</a> and <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> able to open it. At some point, <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a>, who was a <a data-href="Bearer of the Egg" href="remote-blog/factions/bearer-of-the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bearer of the Egg</a>, ran away with the current prodigy-the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy Child</a>-and created <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>, a place where magic was unable to be used by anyone other than Xavier himself. Eventually, <a data-href="Novum Optimus" href="remote-blog/locations/novum-optimus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Novum Optimus</a> laid <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Fall of Scramloria" data-href="Fall of Scramloria" href="remote-blog/events/fall-of-scramloria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">siege</a> upon Scramloria leading to the <a data-href="Prodigy's Disembodiment" href="remote-blog/events/prodigy's-disembodiment.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy's Disembodiment</a>. Only about another 100 years later, the <a data-href="Probot Massacre" href="remote-blog/events/probot-massacre.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Probot Massacre</a> occurs. Shortly after the time that <a data-href="His Weakening" href="remote-blog/events/his-weakening.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">His Weakening</a> occurs, the events of our modern day server will take place.<br><img alt="Timeline (Original).png" src="remote-blog/timeline-(original).png" target="_self">]]></description><link>remote-blog/main-timeline.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Main Timeline.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:39:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deisomnia]]></title><description><![CDATA[Latin for "God's dreams." It is a realm that can only be accessed through the permission of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Prodigy Child</a> and is a section of his subconscious that he can lend out to hold physical forms.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/deisomnia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Deisomnia.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:27:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Affinity]]></title><description><![CDATA[The magical composition of a creature. Upon birth, when the <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy used to make you collapses into the stable magic it is forced to be under the rules of the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>, then the type of variances in how it collapses as <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> lay way for what magics come easiest to you or that can be interacted with by you. For example, this determines what <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> breathe.<br>The more Chaos energy you have, then in general the more affinities you were born with (For example, <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a> wields them all and essentially all other <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> do as well).]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Affinity.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:18:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Legyre]]></title><link>remote-blog/characters/legyre.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Legyre.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 04:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arem]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arem was a dragon during the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a> who, in fear of being eradicated during the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>, quantum-hibernated until a couple millennia later they awoke as <a data-href="Tharem" href="remote-blog/characters/tharem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tharem</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/arem.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Arem.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 06:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[NAHFL]]></title><description><![CDATA[Super AI with a non-corporeal intelligence invented by the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Arthas" data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthans</a> in the <a data-href="Era of Prosperity" href="remote-blog/ages/era-of-prosperity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Era of Prosperity</a>. It stands for "Never Allow Human Filth to Live."]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/nahfl.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/NAHFL.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 05:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chaos Backprocessor]]></title><description><![CDATA[A device invented by the <a data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiods</a> of <a data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthas</a> during the <a data-href="Dragon Age" href="remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Age</a>. It allows for conversion of <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> back into pure <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy, allowing for temporary violations of the spell induced by the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a> beyond the creation of new lifeforms and of the usage of <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/artifacts/chaos-backprocessor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Artifacts/Chaos Backprocessor.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 05:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artho]]></title><description><![CDATA[The first <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Artificiods" data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiod</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/artho.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Artho.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grandun, The Great Dragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Grandun is a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Chaos Dragons" data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragon</a> that chose to stay behind instead of joining the others in <a data-href="Draguia" href="remote-blog/locations/draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draguia</a> upon the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a>. Having been alive since before <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> could even harness <a data-href="Chaos Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/chaos-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Magic</a>, and being one of <a data-href="The First Dragons" href="remote-blog/factions/the-first-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The First Dragons</a>, Grandun is a rather powerful figure. Grandun is the ancestor of all wyrm-type dragons, and is known to change their materialistic form every lunar cycle.<br>Grandun is a rather curious dragon, and he was experimenting with rather intriguing configurations when he came across a clockwork design with which to mold his body from. It was in this form that the people of <a data-href="Arthas" href="remote-blog/locations/arthas.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arthas</a> first came across Grandun, and they began to worship him. Before Grandun departed and changed forms, the people of Arthas struck up an <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> with him, allowing them to create the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Artificiods" data-href="Artificiods" href="remote-blog/races/artificiods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artificiods</a> and have a permanent source of power with which to fuel their most ambitious creations moving forward.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/grandun,-the-great-dragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Grandun, The Great Dragon.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:24:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragon Age]]></title><description><![CDATA[Following the <a data-href="Unification of Magic" href="remote-blog/events/unification-of-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Unification of Magic</a>, other beings began to be born, and the interwoven pieces of <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> would coalesce into various forms of matter. A floating world began to form, and as time advances, so does its size. This world, <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a>, began to be inhabited by all sorts of creations that held different <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Affinity" data-href="Affinity" href="remote-blog/concepts/affinity.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Affinities</a>. Due to the <a data-href="Exchange of Magical Balance" href="remote-blog/events/exchange-of-magical-balance.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Exchange of Magical Balance</a>, <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> began to grow to a level of strength where they were capable of felling dragons, but they needed the motivation. This motivation came in the form of the realization that the magical composition of <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> was the most pure out of any lifeform. As such, humans would harvest dragons for advancing their magical technologies and prowess. Humans reached new heights of magical ascension.<br>Some stronger dragons caught on, but in general humans were hunting dragons to extinction (even if not on purpose) at an alarming rate. <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> however, are so far beyond the scope of human power that they didn't exactly care about what was happening, as dragons of the modern world are viewed as weaker and less than by them. In order to keep themselves separate from the modern world, <a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a> decided to separate all Chaos Dragons away from the rest of reality by creating a pocket dimension within themselves under the spell induced in the <a data-href="Formation of Draguia" href="remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Formation of Draguia</a>. Before fully sealing themselves away, Aternos left behind <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> so that if things did begin to go south, or if otherwise needed, Aternos could interact with the outside world by hatching a new body from The Egg and rebirthing. Following the Formation of Draguia, humans stole The Egg and began to use it for their own purposes, and the Dragon Age came to a close.The time immediately following 0 Cs is unmarked, as the exact time that the Unification of Magic occurred is unknown in it's exact years. As such, the year that the Formation of Draguia occurred is recorded as 0 DA (Meaning Dragon Age) and going closer to the Unification of Magic adds a year for every year in that direction.]]></description><link>remote-blog/ages/dragon-age.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Ages/Dragon Age.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tho-Dragun]]></title><description><![CDATA[Means "broken dragon" in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>. A human with chaos-dragon D.N.A. A Tho-Dragun does not age, nor can one be killed, technically. When a Tho-Dragun is fatally injured, it mutates into a new form with a new soul.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Tho-Dragun.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Whispers of He]]></title><description><![CDATA["I heard it again, those sounds.."]]></description><link>remote-blog/stories/whispers-of-he.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Stories/Whispers of He.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragons]]></title><description><![CDATA[The most magically sensitive race and also the most magically intensive, requiring much more <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy to be formed that other lifeforms.]]></description><link>remote-blog/races/dragons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Races/Dragons.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Map of Scramloria]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="remote-blog/locations/map-of-scramloria.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/map-of-scramloria.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Map of Scramloria.png</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Timeline (Original)]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="remote-blog/timeline-(original).png" target="_self">]]></description><link>remote-blog/timeline-(original).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Timeline (Original).png</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Draconic Magic]]></title><description><![CDATA[A form of <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> that leverages the same power that embodies the <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a> typically through usage of words from the aforementioned language.]]></description><link>remote-blog/magics/draconic-magic.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Magics/Draconic Magic.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tower of the Eternal Eclipse]]></title><description><![CDATA[Located in the heart of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>, this tower serves as a holding place for a powerful artifact that the <a data-href="Order of the Eclipse" href="remote-blog/factions/order-of-the-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Order of the Eclipse</a> put their power together in creating. It uses <a data-href="Draconic Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/draconic-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draconic Magic</a> to hold together the sheer <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> poured into it in its creation. The spell dictates that all other than <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a> within Scramloria are unable to utilize Magic.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/tower-of-the-eternal-eclipse.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Tower of the Eternal Eclipse.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shadow's Peak]]></title><link>remote-blog/locations/shadow&apos;s-peak.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Shadow&apos;s Peak.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mount Daragon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aptly named Mountain "Dragon" as Daragon is "dragon" in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>. This was the resting place of <a data-href="Siethun" href="remote-blog/characters/siethun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Siethun</a> for many eons as <a data-href="Navu" href="remote-blog/locations/navu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Navu</a> had first formed and onwards and is located in <a data-href="Dragonia" href="remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragonia</a>/<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/mount-daragon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Mount Daragon.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragonia]]></title><description><![CDATA[A region that was later tainted by the spell housed in the <a data-href="Tower of the Eternal Eclipse" href="remote-blog/locations/tower-of-the-eternal-eclipse.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tower of the Eternal Eclipse</a> and turned into <a data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)</a>. Prior to this, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragus > Dragus (In the times of Dragonia)" data-href="Dragus#Dragus (In the times of Dragonia)" href="remote-blog/locations/dragus.html#Dragus (In the times of Dragonia)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragus</a> was the capital of Dragonia.]]></description><link>remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Locations/Dragonia.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Order of the Eclipse]]></title><link>remote-blog/factions/order-of-the-eclipse.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Factions/Order of the Eclipse.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prodigy's Disembodiment]]></title><link>remote-blog/events/prodigy&apos;s-disembodiment.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Prodigy&apos;s Disembodiment.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Formation of Draguia]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="Aternos" href="remote-blog/characters/aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aternos</a> created from their corpse a pocket dimension, <a data-href="Draguia" href="remote-blog/locations/draguia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draguia</a>, that all other <a data-href="Chaos Dragons" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos-dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos Dragons</a> could live in uninterupted by the modern world. Aternos left behind <a data-href="The Egg" href="remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Egg</a> and sealed themselves in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" data-href="Zataukeru, Grave of Aternos" href="remote-blog/locations/zataukeru,-grave-of-aternos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zataukeru</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/formation-of-draguia.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Formation of Draguia.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[His Weakening]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Prodigy Child (Probot)" data-href="Prodigy Child (Probot)" href="remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">He Who Watches</a>'s power begins to wane as <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Gareth of Ishoria" data-href="Gareth of Ishoria" href="remote-blog/characters/gareth-of-ishoria.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gareth</a> begins his activity in the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ruins of Scramloria</a>. ]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/his-weakening.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/His Weakening.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exchange of Magical Balance]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a> take a much greater amount more of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> energy to be born, and thus in comparison to other lifeforms they can only exist in much smaller numbers. This is because dragons don't procreate nearly as much as most modern creatures, and so especially as <a data-href="Humans" href="remote-blog/races/humans.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Humans</a> began to be born more and more, the dragon populations took a significant decline. Furthermore, not only was there less <a data-href="Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Magic</a> so less dragons were born, but the dragons that were born were beginning to have progressively weaker and weaker magic as a result. This allowed for other lifeforms to finally begin to be more powerful than dragons, even if only by numbers.Some dragons began to be born with no affinities, as opposed to having been born almost always with several as in the past.]]></description><link>remote-blog/events/exchange-of-magical-balance.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Events/Exchange of Magical Balance.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nightfall]]></title><description><![CDATA[The barrier falling ]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/nightfall.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Nightfall.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oath]]></title><link>remote-blog/concepts/oath.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Oath.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dragon Tongue]]></title><description><![CDATA[The language used by <a data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragons</a>. It carries a certain weight to its words as it was forged in the very essence of <a data-href="Chaos" href="remote-blog/concepts/chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Chaos</a> itself at the dawn of time during the <a data-href="Age of Chaos" href="remote-blog/ages/age-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Age of Chaos</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Concepts/Dragon Tongue.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tharem]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tharem was a <a data-href="Tho-Dragun" href="remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tho-Dragun</a>. They were created from the transformative process of quantum-hibernation by <a data-href="Arem" href="remote-blog/characters/arem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Arem</a>. Tharem lived ~500 years until being fatally injured in a war. This resulted in Tharem's mutation into <a data-href="Inkiab" href="remote-blog/characters/inkiab.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Inkiab</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/tharem.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Tharem.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xavier]]></title><link>remote-blog/characters/xavier.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Xavier.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sintel, Keeper of Halüges]]></title><description><![CDATA[Halüges meaning "history" in <a data-href="Dragon Tongue" href="remote-blog/concepts/dragon-tongue.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragon Tongue</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/sintel,-keeper-of-halüges.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Sintel, Keeper of Halüges.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prodigy Child (Probot)]]></title><link>remote-blog/characters/prodigy-child-(probot).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Prodigy Child (Probot).md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Siethun]]></title><description><![CDATA[A <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dragons" data-href="Dragons" href="remote-blog/races/dragons.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dragon</a> that was worshipped by the people of <a data-href="Dragonia" href="remote-blog/locations/dragonia.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dragonia</a> for millennia before being trapped within <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" data-href="Scramloria (The Sunless Realm)" href="remote-blog/locations/scramloria-(the-sunless-realm).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Scramloria</a> where he would inevitably be killed by <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Sintel, Keeper of Halüges" data-href="Sintel, Keeper of Halüges" href="remote-blog/characters/sintel,-keeper-of-halüges.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sintel</a> in order to sever the <a data-href="Oath" href="remote-blog/concepts/oath.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oath</a> between him and <a data-href="Xavier" href="remote-blog/characters/xavier.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Xavier</a> allowing for usage of advanced <a data-href="Draconic Magic" href="remote-blog/magics/draconic-magic.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Draconic Magic</a>. Siethun took refuge within <a data-href="Mount Daragon" href="remote-blog/locations/mount-daragon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mount Daragon</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/siethun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Siethun.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inkiab]]></title><description><![CDATA[Inkiab, <a data-href="Tho-Dragun" href="remote-blog/races/tho-dragun.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tho-Dragun</a>, and son of <a data-href="Tharem" href="remote-blog/characters/tharem.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tharem</a>, lived almost a millennium until he passed away and mutated into <a data-href="Aivener" href="remote-blog/characters/aivener.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aivener</a>.]]></description><link>remote-blog/characters/inkiab.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Characters/Inkiab.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Egg]]></title><link>remote-blog/artifacts/the-egg.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">remote-blog/Artifacts/The Egg.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:14:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>